Antonio J. Franceschi

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with over 2 years of experience coding websites using modern technologies and over 15 years of experience troubleshooting and solving problems in the IT Operations field. In the past year I have also mentored and tutored Web Development Bootcamp students.

Bilingual: English - Spanish

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address

1825 SW 67th CT Miami, FL 33155

CONTACT

ajfranceschi@icloud.com



305.804.4248



ajfranceschi.com



github.com/ajfranceschi



linkedin.com/in/ajfranceschi

EDUCATION

University of Puerto Rico

Bachelor's in Business Administration Management Information Systems (MIS)

FreeCodeCamp.org

Front End Libraries JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Responsive Web Design

Zero To Mastery Academy

The Complete React Developer in 2020 The Complete Web Developer in 2019

Udemv

The Complete Web Developer Course 2.0

edX PennX

SD4x: Programming for the Web with JS

Devslopes

Beginner Full Stack Web Development

SKILLS

- HTML
- **jQuery**
- React Router
- MongoDB
- Sass

- **CSS**
- ReactJS
- NodeJS
- PostgreSQL
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React Redux
- ExpressJS
- MySQL
- RESTful API

CERTIFICATIONS

- Front End Libraries
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures
- Responsive Web Design
- Complete React Developer in 2020
- The Complete Web Developer in 2019: Zero to Mastery
- SD4x: Programming for the Web with JavaScript
- Microsoft Certified Systems Administrator
- Apple Certified Macintosh Technician
- CompTIA Network+
- CompTIA A+

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Associate L2, Team Lead, Field Ops

Lion Re:Sources, Publicis Groupe

2017 - 2020

- Increase productivity of a team of 8 technicians by providing continuous feedback and support.
- · Coordinate with vendors the procurement, installation and repair of company owned equipment.
- Increase end user satisfaction and team members productivity by creating and facilitating trainings.
- Lead infrastructure equipment refresh projects.
- Create and maintain Active Directory objects when warranted.

Operations Analyst, Field Ops

Lion Re:Sources, Publicis Groupe

2011 - 2017

- Support more than 400 on-site and remote users, including Executives, on Macintosh, Windows and mobile devices.
- Minimized downtime by monitoring servers and networking gear.
- Install and fix server and networking equipment.
- Test new technologies and ensure compatibility with existing environment before placing into production.
- Minimize A/V downtime by troubleshooting and repairing issues.

Desktop Support Technician

Our Kids of Miami Dade & Monroe

2009-2011

- Provide end user support to over 400 end users.
- Diagnose and troubleshoot Mac and PC equipment, DSL connectivity issues.
- Decrease equipment deployment time to completion by creating and maintaining Operating System images for all our devices.
- Create and maintain Active Directory objects.
- Train newly hired technicians.
- Communicate daily with other IT departments for escalation and coordinate end user support.